<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <channel>
    <title>COEY Cast</title>
    <link>https://coey.com/resources/podcast</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2025 COEY</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:10:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <itunes:category text="Business">
      <itunes:category text="Entrepreneurship"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Technology">
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>

    <generator>RSS Builder</generator>

    <!-- Show description -->
    <description>
      COEY Cast is your daily download on AI and automation. We break down the latest in generative models, intelligent workflows, and emerging tools—giving marketers, operators, and business leaders the insights they need to move faster and scale smarter. From AI video and audio to end-to-end automation pipelines, each episode turns complex breakthroughs into clear, actionable takeaways you can actually use.
    </description>

    <!-- iTunes / Apple Podcasts tags -->
    <itunes:author>COEY</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
      COEY Cast is your daily download on AI and automation. We break down the latest in generative models, intelligent workflows, and emerging tools—giving marketers, operators, and business leaders the insights they need to move faster and scale smarter. From AI video and audio to end-to-end automation pipelines, each episode turns complex breakthroughs into clear, actionable takeaways you can actually use.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/brand-assets/coey-cast-logo.jpg"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>COEY</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>ted@coey.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

    <!-- Atom self-link -->
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ted-coey/coey-cast/main/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <!-- Episodes will be inserted here as <item> blocks -->

  <item>
    <title>Qwen3-Max-Preview: Scaling to a Trillion &amp; Beyond</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This week, we put Alibaba’s Qwen3-Max-Preview to the test—a trillion-parameter upgrade promising smoother instruction following, longer conversational threads, and genuine tool-calling power for creators and teams. We discuss what “scaling works” actually means for daily workflows: less prompt wrangling, better agents for chaining tasks, and practical examples like video content pipelines and brand campaigns. We break down the differences from previous Qwen3 models, compare real-world pros and cons, and share best practices for validation, safety, and using multi-step automations. By the end, you’ll know how Qwen3-Max-Preview can streamline content ops and whether it’s worth plugging into your stack, solo or at scale.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 22:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250906175146600+-+qwen3_max_scaling_vibes.mp3" length="4197360" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757196141766</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250906175146600+-+qwen3_max_scaling_vibes.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Seven Ways to Keep Your AI Video in Line: Vidu Q1 Update</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode dives into the massive Reference-to-Video update for ShengShu Technology’s Vidu Q1 model, which now lets users upload up to seven reference images per sequence. Hunter and Riley unpack what this means for creators, brands, and indie studios striving for true shot-to-shot consistency in AI-generated video. They explore how multiple references help lock character identity, props, wardrobe, and backgrounds, reducing the notorious continuity drift. Expect a breakdown of workflow tips, common pitfalls, competitive comparisons with Runway and Luma, use cases from social content to ad pipelines, and where this tech sits in the growing stack for marketers and content teams. Don’t miss practical advice on setting up your own "reference kit".]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:17:54 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250908170128634+-+vidu_q1_seven_refs.mp3" length="4689288" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757366274333</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250908170128634+-+vidu_q1_seven_refs.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Firefly Boards &amp; Model 4: Idea to Approval Fast-Tracked</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Today, we battle test Microsoft VibeVoice 7B and dive deep into Adobe’s Firefly Image Model 4 and Firefly Boards. Discover what makes Model 4 a leap ahead for creatives. Hands and eyes look human, image quality is up, and styles stay consistent across channels and platforms. Firefly Boards lets you co-create, share, get feedback, and iterate— all right inside Creative Cloud, without back-and-forth emails. Automation tips abound: learn to trigger batch image and video generation from intake forms, streamline approvals, and nail brand consistency. Pros, cons, and practical workflow hacks for solo creators, marketers, and global teams are covered. Plus, the automation blueprint to get your campaigns from prompt to publish with less busywork.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250909185413964+-+firefly_boards_model4.mp3" length="3478248" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757459079525</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/firefly.png"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Unlimited B-Roll Bonanza: Envato’s AI Video September</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Dive into this episode where we break down Envato's game-changing move to lift AI video generation limits in VideoGen for all of September. Learn how creators, marketers, and agencies can generate unlimited AI-powered videos, leveraging powerful models like Google Veo 3 and Kling. We walk through smart workflows, automation hacks, and practical advice for building b-roll libraries, all while securing lifetime commercial licenses for every video made this month. Hear tips for prompt-writing, quality control, and maximizing your creative output. Plus, get the lowdown on how Envato’s all-you-can-generate September compares to Runway, Pika, and Luma. Whether you’re a solo content creator or an enterprise team, this episode is your blueprint for making the most of unlimited AI video.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:35:36 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250910171633569+-+envato_unlimited_sept.mp3" length="3758232" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757540136233</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/envato-video-gen.png"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Unchunk the Funk: Exploring Nvidia Rubin CPX</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode is a deep dive into Nvidia's Rubin CPX, the new AI chip designed to revolutionize long-form generative media. We explain how CPX combines lightning-fast media engines with massive context memory, putting an end to mid-project memory loss and timeline fragmentation. Discover the tech behind real-time dubbing that captures performance, code copilots that see your whole repository, and enterprise use cases for seamless translation and editing. We break down numbers, architecture, and the real impact for creators, marketers, and solo podcasters. Hear about upcoming workflows, cost economics, competition, and potential pitfalls. If you want to future-proof your creative pipeline and see how hardware is finally keeping up with creatives, this one’s for you.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250911091308249+-+unchunk_the_funk.mp3" length="3887232" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757597424558</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250911091308249+-+unchunk_the_funk.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>AI Highlights: Synamedia’s Stack Powers Smart Streaming</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode breaks down Synamedia’s bold move at IBC 2025 as they launch a stacked AI layer for video pros—creators, broadcasters, and streamers. Riley and Hunter explore how conversational search brings instant highlight discovery, live tagging powers fast editing, and creative personalization delivers tailored promos for key segments. Learn how the new multi-CDN switching and ContentArmor watermarking tech make livestreams more reliable and secure. Plus, we dive into Synamedia’s open standards push, AI-powered quality tuning, and the blend of creative and operational gains. If you work with video at any scale, this episode covers why Synamedia’s AI stack might change your workflow—from auto-tagging goals to cutting bandwidth bills and getting content out faster.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250911121255830+-+synamedia_ai_stack.mp3" length="3332952" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757608523178</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250911121255830+-+synamedia_ai_stack.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Agentic Marketing: Adobe’s AEP Agents Take the Wheel</title>
    <description><![CDATA[In this episode, Hunter and Riley break down Adobe’s launch of AI-powered agents inside the Adobe Experience Platform (AEP), featuring the new Agent Orchestrator. Learn how six specialized agents—Audience, Journey, Experimentation, Data Insights, Site Optimization, and Product Support—work together to automate segmentation, journeys, testing, reporting, site updates, and customer support. Discover practical use cases, potential risks, and the impact for marketing ops and enterprise teams. The hosts discuss real workflow savings and why this shifts agentic marketing from hype to reality. Whether you’re a marketer in a large org or a solo creator curious about automation patterns, you’ll get actionable insights and ways to apply the blueprint to your own stack.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:55:33 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250913114339799+-+adobe_agent_orchestrator.mp3" length="3516600" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757778933486</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250913114339799+-+adobe_agent_orchestrator.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Ollama on ARM: Local LLMs Go Pro, No Cloud Needed</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode dives into Ollama’s latest update: true native support for Apple Silicon, Linux ARM, and Windows on ARM—plus automatic GPU acceleration. Hunter and Riley break down what this means for creators, marketers, and teams who want fast, private, and scalable local AI without the cloud headaches. Discover how to automate copywriting, captions, content moderation, product Q&A, and more with local LLMs that actually ship real projects. Get practical workflow tips for solo makers, agency teams, and brands—including how to wire up n8n for end-to-end automation. Learn where local AI now beats the cloud in speed, privacy, and cost, what hardware you’ll need, and what snags to expect on day one. Local workflow, global impact.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 18:59:32 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250916143942398+-+ollama_arm_llm_pro.mp3" length="3934560" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758049172016</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250916143942398+-+ollama_arm_llm_pro.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Persona-Party: Meta AI Studio Slides Into DMs</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode dives into Meta’s newly launched AI Studio, a no-code platform for spinning up custom AI characters directly in Instagram, Messenger, WhatsApp, and web. Learn how creators and brands can deploy persona-driven assistants in hours, gather audience insights, and streamline DM engagement—without developers. The hosts cover real-world use cases for solo creators, D2C brands, agencies, and enterprise teams, examining automation possibilities, integration limits, pricing, and competitive landscape. You’ll get quick tips for campaign ideation, lead qualification, and making the most of current API options like WhatsApp Cloud and Instagram Messaging flows. Plus, hear why this is a must-have for DM-heavy brands and what unlocks true orchestration whenever public APIs arrive. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:46:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250917142834025+-+meta_ai_studio_dm.mp3" length="3990864" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758134784320</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250917142834025+-+meta_ai_studio_dm.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Zoom AI Companion 3.0: Avatars, Notes &amp; 60FPS Oh My!</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode crash-tests Zoom AI Companion 3.0, just announced at Zoomtopia. We dig into photorealistic avatars that mirror your every move, cross-platform automatic meeting notes that work in Zoom, Teams, and Google Meet, and agent-style scheduling that might finally end meeting exhaustion. We break down who benefits most—from solo creators who want flawless presence to marketing managers juggling endless calls. There’s a look at HD and 60FPS video upgrades, new automation potential, and bold pricing moves that challenge notetaker apps like Otter and Fireflies. Tune in for tips on integrating AI Companion into your workflow, honest caveats, security pointers, and skeptical optimism about the future of AI-powered meetings. Plus, plenty of memes about sending your avatar instead.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250919151209683+-+zoom_ai_companion_3.mp3" length="3698736" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758312116753</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250919151209683+-+zoom_ai_companion_3.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Voxel Revolution: Hunyuan 3D 3.0 Unleashed</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Dive into Hunyuan 3D 3.0 by Tencent, the latest leap in text or image-to-3D generation. Hosts Hunter and Riley dissect its features, including boosted accuracy, denser geometry, sharper edges, and the standout ability to reconstruct hidden parts of objects. Learn how new automation options with API access can overhaul your workflow for e-commerce, games, social content, and more. The episode explores practical use cases for creators and organizations, workflow integration tips, pricing, file compatibility, and the realities versus the hype. Plus, get a quick-start playbook to test it in your pipeline. Whether you craft digital assets for fun or run a 3D factory, this episode arms you with what’s new, what works, and where to watch out.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:44:47 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250920122738555+-+hunyuan_3d_voxel_cast.mp3" length="3990552" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758390287405</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250920122738555+-+hunyuan_3d_voxel_cast.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Ray3 &amp; Firefly: AI Video Levels Up in Adobe’s Playground</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Dive into Luma’s Ray3, now turbocharging Adobe Firefly with ten-second AI video generation, native HDR in ACES EXR, and scene-level planning. We break down what 'reasoning' for video means and why direct handoff into Creative Cloud is such a big deal for creators and marketers. From quick Draft Mode explorations to full quality cinematic moments, Ray3’s integration offers workflow magic: brand-safe templating, fixed color pipelines, and time-saving edits. We cover draft vs final workflows, competitive pressure for Runway and Pika, automation possibilities, limitations, and real-world applications for TikTokers, marketers, and small teams. Is this a toy or essential tool? We map out who should care and what comes next in the pipeline!]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:52:09 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250921152924557+-+ray3_firefly_workflows.mp3" length="3246600" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758484329712</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250921152924557+-+ray3_firefly_workflows.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Wardrobe Wizardry: Decart Lucy Edit Dev &amp; Pro Breakdown</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Get a backstage pass to Decart’s latest release: Lucy Edit Dev, the open-weight, text-guided video editor you can actually download and run locally. Riley and Hunter break down how prompt-based video edits preserve your camera moves while swapping outfits, backgrounds, or brands—with no reshoots. We dig into real-world uses for creators, brands, and marketers, from programmatic wardrobe changes to instant localization and product placement, all while keeping creative control in your workflow. Plus, we explain the Dev vs Pro lane, commercial licensing, and how this AI leapfrogs closed competitors like Runway and Pika. Whether you’re solo or scaling, discover how Lucy Edit can transform editing from timeline-first to brief-first in your postproduction pipeline.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250922203038646+-+lucy_edit_wizardry.mp3" length="4074144" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758588233826</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250922203038646+-+lucy_edit_wizardry.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Meet Qwen3-Omni: Your Real-Time Multimodal Sidekick</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode puts Alibaba’s new Qwen3-Omni model under the microscope. We break down what makes it special: sub-second talkback, open weights, and the power to process and generate text, images, audio, and video—all in real time. Learn what the 'thinker–talker' architecture actually does, why self-hosting matters for control, and how Qwen3-Omni simplifies the whole stack for creators, brands, and developers. We cover hands-on scenarios: live captions for TikTokers, automated show notes for podcasters, multilingual review rooms for marketers, and more. Compare Qwen3-Omni to GPT-4o and Gemini, see how to wire it up with n8n or your own orchestrator, and get straight takes on voice quality, governance, rollout plans, and real-world risks. Automation just got a voice.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:37:14 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250923101208973+-+qwen3_omni_real_time.mp3" length="3719160" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758638234154</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250923101208973+-+qwen3_omni_real_time.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Kling 2.5 Turbo: From Wobbly to Wow!</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode of COEY Cast explores the release of Kling 2.5 Turbo, the newest AI video generation model making waves for its major reliability upgrade. Hunter and Riley explain how smoother motion, better frame-to-frame coherence, and improved prompt matching make this version a step change for creators and teams. They detail how the model reduces “AI-wobbly” moments, accelerates production, and delivers more usable first drafts with fewer artifacts. You’ll learn how agencies, solo creators, and brands can automate workflows, integrate Kling 2.5 Turbo with platforms like Atlabs and ImagineArt, and speed up approvals. The hosts cover benchmark results, ecosystem trends, practical scenarios, and key caveats to help you decide if Kling 2.5 Turbo should power your next project.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:16:41 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250925153150813+-+kling_25_turbo_wow.mp3" length="4114272" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758835001675</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250925153150813+-+kling_25_turbo_wow.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Sync or Swim: Alibaba Wan 2.5-Preview Puts Audio First</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Today’s Coey Cast dives deep into Alibaba’s Wan 2.5-Preview, the all-in-one model that generates videos with audio perfectly synced—no glue code, no post-sync headaches. Hosts Hunter and Riley put it through its paces, exploring how this model handles text, image, video, and audio in a single pass. They break down the workflow for creators, marketers, and ops teams, show practical automations with n8n and Zapier, and spell out its current limits. Learn how region-specific endpoints, optional watermarks, and predictable handling of audio tracks can speed up your ad variants, product reels, and explainer clips. Whether you’re a solo creative or scaling brand, this episode spotlights why seamless audio-video generation is a game changer.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:20:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250926060423424+-+sync_or_swim_wan25.mp3" length="3714840" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758882045742</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250926060423424+-+sync_or_swim_wan25.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Meta Vibes: Is AI Video Getting Viral Instantly?</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Dive into Meta’s newest launch: Vibes, an AI-powered short video creation and remix feed built straight into the Meta AI app and web. We break down how Vibes collapses the workflow from idea to publish, making it easy to generate, remix, and distribute videos across Meta’s social channels. Learn who it’s for, how it compares to other platforms like TikTok, YouTube Shorts, and standalone AI editors, and what shifts for creators, brands, and marketers. We cover the competitive landscape, workflow improvements, and the risks of “AI slop.” Plus, get a hands-on playbook for rapid A/B testing, community remixing, and keeping your content fun and original. If fast feedback and integrated growth are your game, this episode is your playbook.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 19:39:05 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250926151259180+-+meta_vibes_ai_video.mp3" length="3718896" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1758915545406</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250926151259180+-+meta_vibes_ai_video.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Sora 2: From Model Theater to Vibe Engine</title>
    <description><![CDATA[In this episode, Hunter and Riley demo and dissect Sora 2, OpenAI’s new standalone text-to-video app for creating swipable, ten-second vertical clips. They explore how Sora 2’s unified audio/visual generation streamlines workflow for creators, marketers, and founders, making it perfect for testing hooks, brand teasers, and product loops. The hosts break down what’s new, who benefits, where enterprise features fall short, and how Sora compares to Google Veo, Runway, and Pika. They highlight impacts on speed, cost, and creative flexibility and warn about rights, guardrails, and export limits. Tune in for actionable strategies and expert takes on using Sora 2 as a testbed for modern short-form content.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:56:27 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250930153649481+-+sora_2_vibe_engine.mp3" length="3952344" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1759262187604</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250930153649481+-+sora_2_vibe_engine.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Halve the Cost, Double the Vibes: DeepSeek&apos;s AI Shakeup</title>
    <description><![CDATA[In this episode, Hunter and Riley take a hands-on dive into DeepSeek’s brand new AI model that claims to cut usage costs in half. They break down the technical magic—like smarter routing and sparse attention—that makes these savings possible and discuss the practical impact for creators, agencies, and content teams. The hosts outline when and where this matters most, how to benchmark it in your workflow, and which teams should be watching out for new pricing wars. Expect tactical ideas, honest cautions on regional access and compliance, and creative strategies to maximize cheap tokens. The show was 100% AI-produced using Microsoft VibeVoice 7B, staying true to their “weird in, weird out” ethos. Listen for fast insights and real talk.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:43:35 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251001112016245+-+deepseek_token_drop.mp3" length="2884656" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1759337015235</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251001112016245+-+deepseek_token_drop-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Sonnet 4.5: Automation Gets Its Groove Back</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode is a deep dive into Anthropic's Claude Sonnet 4.5, focusing on its strengths as a long-running, tool-savvy AI agent for creators, marketers, and enterprise teams. We break down how Sonnet 4.5 automates everything from spreadsheet chores and bug fixes to content calendars and podcast workflows, while still leaving humans in control for publishing and approvals. Learn how distribution through AWS Bedrock and Google Cloud Vertex unlocks simple integration and enterprise-grade security. We cover the shift from flashy demos to reliable workflow execution, discuss crucial guardrails like permissions and auditability, and explain how small teams can reclaim hours every week. Plus: comparisons, use cases, and the latest on automation trends for content, code, and campaign management.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251001154136446+-+sonnet_45_auto_groove.mp3" length="3492288" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1759348674298</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251001154136446+-+sonnet_45_auto_groove-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title>Open Outputs: HunyuanImage 3.0 Hits the Workflow</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Tencent’s HunyuanImage 3.0 lands with open weights and inference code ready for creative operators—not just cloud providers. We dig into how unified text and image streams up your prompt game, boost scene coherence, and make enterprise-level automation a reality. Learn why campaign workhorses like agencies, studios, and brands might ditch pay-per-render for predictable, process-friendly setups. Discover practical tips on fine tuning, asset audit trails, and smooth integration with existing queues and DAMs. We cover real benchmarks and the hands-on developer know-how you’ll need to get started—all with a realistic look at licensing, VRAM, and typography quirks. Control, customization, and creative ops just leveled up.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:58:53 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251002214633314+-+hunyuanimage_3_power.mp3" length="3981744" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1759456733128</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251002214633314+-+hunyuanimage_3_power-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Granite 4.0: The Compliance Brain That Ships</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Granite 4.0 from IBM is purpose-built for work that matters. Hybrid-first design, lower GPU bills, and real enterprise controls make it a standout for teams buried in docs, briefs, and policies. Learn how its new sequence modeling powers long-form extraction, drafting, and workflow-ready batch jobs. From agency content factories to regulated industries, discover how Granite 4.0 lets you automate more without giving up audit trails or data control. Get concrete scenarios for brands, creators, and support teams who need batches done fast—and safely. Explore why hardware flexibility and deployment options matter for scaling co-creation.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251003125516264+-+granite_40_compliance_brain.mp3" length="4905984" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1759511640589</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251003125516264+-+granite_40_compliance_brain-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>
       

  <item>
    <title>Realtime APIs and Prompt Caching: AI That Talks Back</title>
    <description><![CDATA[OpenAI just dropped a slate of pragmatic features for creators and marketers: Realtime API for sub-second voice experiences, vision fine-tuning for on-brand images and videos, prompt caching for faster, cheaper outputs, and distillation for nimble, customizable mini-models. From smooth product page concierges to auto QA for ads, this is about practical automation you can actually wire up now. Less hype, more shipping your workflow upgrades. We cover how these API-level features can boost control, slash costs, and plug straight into your existing stack—plus tips to avoid classic ops pitfalls.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 21:43:36 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251006165245013+-+realtime_prompt_caching.mp3" length="3484128" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1759787016594</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251006165245013+-+realtime_prompt_caching-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Moondream 3: Count It, Tag It, Ship It</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Moondream 3 isn’t just another vision-language demo. This episode dives into how Moondream 3 turns asset chaos into reliable, automated workflows for creators, marketers, and brands. Discover why its precision tagging, open-vocabulary detection, and sneaky-good counting unlock real automation you can trust. Learn how to auto-tag photo libraries, run compliance checks, and extract info from charts—without babysitting every image. Get into the specifics: stronger object tracking, chart extraction, fewer hallucinations, plus where Moondream 3 stands against Google’s Gemini and OpenAI’s latest. From TikTok clips to campaign visuals, see how this vision model plugs into real creative pipelines. Less scroll, more ship.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:12:41 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251012161713312+-+moondream_3_auto_tag.mp3" length="3832152" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1760314361998</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251012161713312+-+moondream_3_auto_tag-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Bots That Click: Agents Break Out of the Chatbox</title>
    <description><![CDATA[AI agents are breaking free from chat and getting actual work done. We dig into Amazon Q powering governed automation across your stack, Anthropic Claude Code plugins making team workflows slicker, and Google Gemini 2.5 Computer Use letting bots click, type, and submit on real web interfaces. If you've ever dreamt of skipping browser chores, smarter asset approvals, or finally taming tool sprawl, this is for you. We cover concrete automations for creators and content teams, all with humans in the approval loop. Workflow changes, cost breakdowns, and spicy gotchas included.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:40:57 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251013210946994+-+bots_that_click.mp3" length="4583376" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1760406057269</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251013210946994+-+bots_that_click-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Penny Motion: Kandinsky-5 &amp; the Five-Cent Video Revolution</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Short-form video just got a seismic cost drop. This episode unpacks Fal.ai’s new Kandinsky-5 text-to-video public endpoints, where five-second and ten-second videos cost pocket change and fit right into automated workflows. From TikTok hooks to ecommerce motion tiles, meme overlays, and ad variant factories, creators and marketers can now batch video like never before. Learn who should plug in today, what workflows this flips, how to run spend-safe experiments, and why penny-priced clips change the math for creative teams of any size. Includes practical automation tactics and limitations to keep your process smart.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:26:36 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251014192608662+-+kandinsky5_penny_motion.mp3" length="4310952" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1760487996896</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251014192608662+-+kandinsky5_penny_motion-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Frame Perfect: Google Veo 3.1 Levels Up Short Videos</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Google Veo 3.1 is stepping out of demo-land and into reliable, production-ready territory for creators and marketers. The magic? Full control over vertical 9:16 output and precise first and last frame selection, all through the Gemini API. No more wrestling to hit your CTA; now you can pin branded frames exactly where you want. We break down what this means for social teams, automation nerds, ad agencies, and localization pros. Plus: workflows that ship, the Sora vs Veo debate, automation tips, and why feed-native video is all about effective endings. Smart config, fewer fixes, tighter budgets, happier editors.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251015133613699+-+frame_perfect_veo31.mp3" length="3696888" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1760551404804</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251015133613699+-+frame_perfect_veo31-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Microsoft MAI-Image-1: No More Tab-Hopping for Creators</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Microsoft jumps into image generation with MAI-Image-1, now built right into PowerPoint, Word, Designer, and Bing. This episode breaks down what the new model means for creators, marketers, and anyone running campaigns in Microsoft 365 land. We cover hands-on workflow upgrades, where MAI-Image-1 stands out (and where it doesn’t), and quick-win automations like instant moodboards and storyboards without leaving your doc. Learn when to use Microsoft’s native feature, where to stick with open models, and how to measure real-world ROI. Compliance, governance, and brand safety get a boost, but you’ll still want human eyes on the final cut.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:13:36 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251016065740724+-+mai_image1_microsoft_ep.mp3" length="3511512" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1760620416899</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251016065740724+-+mai_image1_microsoft_ep-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>PaddleOCR-VL: Layout Legends and Doc Automation Wins</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Unlock the world of document automation with PaddleOCR-VL, the lean, mean, structure-reading machine taking over PDF parsing. From invoices to multilingual research, creators and teams can automate their grind—extracting tables, formulas, charts, and more—right where the data lives. This episode breaks down the tech, who it helps, and how it stacks up against closed services like Azure and Google Document AI. Expect workflow real talk, battle-tested advice, clear gotchas, and ship-it kits for creators, agencies, and enterprises ready to ditch manual doc wrangling for good.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 09:13:10 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251018044110164+-+paddleocr_vl_doc_magic.mp3" length="4231728" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1760778790067</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251018044110164+-+paddleocr_vl_doc_magic-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Live Video Glow-Ups: Krea’s Realtime Remix Revolution</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Krea Realtime 14B is turning live video into a real-time creative playground for streamers, event teams, and brands. Swipe from neon anime to ink wash on air, driven by the crowd or automation—not after the fact. We unpack its cache-powered stability, instant feedback, and why it’s not quite plug-and-play. Expect workflow tips, ops stacks, competitive context, and brand safety hacks. Plus: why the tech isn’t the story—the magic is what humans do with it live.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:55:35 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251021072251485+-+krea_realtime_live_magic.mp3" length="3417624" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761047735304</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251021072251485+-+krea_realtime_live_magic-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>DeepSeek-OCR: Shrink Your Docs Not Your Hustle</title>
    <description><![CDATA[DeepSeek-OCR just landed and it’s flipping the script for anyone sick of wrestling with giant PDFs, weird tables, and messy document pipelines. This episode unpacks how its pixel-compression-first approach slashes token costs and brings layout fidelity to the masses. From solo creators converting scanned handouts to enterprise teams automating compliance, discover fresh ways to automate, summarize, and search long docs. Get real workflow upgrades, practical use cases, competitive context with PaddleOCR-VL, and tips for smooth implementation. Plus, meme breaks. If you’ve got documents with structure (and headaches), you’re going to want to hear how “compress, then decode” saves real budget and time—minus the drama.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:55:44 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251021163801892+-+deepseek_ocr_compression.mp3" length="3582816" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761080144648</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251021163801892+-+deepseek_ocr_compression-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Atlas Shrugged Off Your Tabs: OpenAI’s New Browser Play</title>
    <description><![CDATA[ChatGPT Atlas has landed and it's not just another tab in your digital chaos. Atlas is an AI-native browser that turns your open tabs into completed tasks. Get the scoop on on-page summarization, Agent Mode that actually interacts with websites for you, and privacy controls that let you share or nuke context at will. See how creators, brand teams, and operators can move from research to first drafts fast without the usual browser thrash. We compare Atlas to Google’s Computer Use, Bardeen, and Arc Search—explaining the where, why, and how for your workflow. No overhype, just what it means for your creative output.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 01:35:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251022203735666+-+atlas_tabs_to_tasks.mp3" length="3519864" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761183345923</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251022203735666+-+atlas_tabs_to_tasks-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>From Pocket to Powerhouse: Qwen3-VL and Meshy 6 Level Up</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Qwen3-VL just dropped two new vision-language models—one tiny enough to run on your phone for instant AR, brand checks, and field ops, and a 32B beast for deep enterprise automation like hours-long video review and multi-doc audits. Meanwhile, Meshy 6 Preview is making 3D asset pipelines smoother with sharper geometry and fewer cleanup headaches. This episode unpacks where these tools shine for creators, marketers, and media teams automating visual workflows. Get practical use cases, cost vibes, and smart advice to blend creativity with machine speed—without getting lost in the GPU bill.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251023133955474+-+qwen3vl_meshy6.mp3" length="3878016" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761252611714</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251023133955474+-+qwen3vl_meshy6-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>LTX-2: Sync or Swim? Automating Video with a Side of Audio</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Lightricks just launched LTX-2, claiming first place for open-source video models that actually sync audio and 4K visuals in a single pass. Ready for creators, marketers, and teams sick of post-production headaches. Get the scoop on native 4K, 10-second cap, multi-keyframe continuity, and creative automation that drops costs instead of frames. Hear how API access, creative studio, and open code can actually slot into real pipelines—plus what’s real on self-hosting, cost math, and production readiness. Quick hits on DeepSeek’s price war and how pipeline-first AI is flipping the script for content ops. If you’re chasing faster workflows, synced sound, and more time for what matters, this is your playbook.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:51:38 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251024070424492+-+ltx2_sync_or_swim.mp3" length="3450120" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761306698649</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251024070424492+-+ltx2_sync_or_swim-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>From JPEG to Jiggle-Proof: Seed3D’s 1-Click 3D Revolution</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Seed3D 1.0 from ByteDance takes a single image and spits out a simulation-ready 3D asset, watertight and ready for production. No downloading repos or wrangling GPUs—just upload and automate. Discover how this API-first, closed model lets ecommerce, gaming, and robotics teams scale asset creation fast. Get step-by-step workflow ideas, real-world limits around fidelity and materials, and tactical tips for integrating into content supply chains, with plenty of reality checks on where human review still shines. Plus, a rapid-fire tour through other trending AI video and 3D tools.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 12:44:11 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251025081738903+-+seed3d_jiggle_proof.mp3" length="4201872" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761396251535</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251025081738903+-+seed3d_jiggle_proof-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Open Source Agents with Bite: Tongyi DeepResearch Unleashed</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Alibaba has open-sourced Tongyi DeepResearch, a research agent with real web-browsing smarts and full citation trails. With code on GitHub and a friendly license, you can run it yourself and wire it into your own stack—think Slack, Notion, or even custom compliance dashboards. Under the hood, a mixture-of-experts model means you get efficiency for solo creators and scale for small teams. This episode covers workflows for weekly trend scans, competitor tracking, and campaign prep with cited sources at every step. There are no glossy APIs, but total control and privacy if you need it. Hear how open web research agents let marketers, creators, and ops teams automate the grunt work and focus on the strategy, not the doomscrolling.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 18:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251026135125844+-+tongyi_deepresearch_ep.mp3" length="3386952" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761503040298</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251026135125844+-+tongyi_deepresearch_ep-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Costco Beats Champagne: Qualcomm and Intel Shake Up AI Inference</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Nvidia’s got the bottle service, but Qualcomm and Intel just crashed the party with Costco-sized savings. Qualcomm’s AI200 and AI250 and Intel’s Crescent Island promise cheaper AI inference and memory-rich accelerators that upend Nvidia’s stranglehold on creative and marketing workflows. This episode breaks down what this means for scaling LLMs, batch video variants, and TTS dubbing, plus how it impacts platform costs, vendor lock-in, and real creative automation. Get practical plays for marketers, creators, and anyone building scalable media ops. It’s a cost curve moment for AI that’s all about more output, less pipeline pain, and new options for every team size.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 18:18:57 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251027135850072+-+qualcomm_intel_ai_cost.mp3" length="3436032" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761589137585</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251027135850072+-+qualcomm_intel_ai_cost-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Pico-Banana: The Dataset That Peels Back Image Edits</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Apple’s Pico‑Banana‑400K is shaking up text-guided image editing by going real—not synthetic—with 400,000 photo triplets. We cover why this new dataset matters for anyone benchmarking or building image-editing automation, from marketers struggling with artifact-riddled mockups to devs craving models that finally follow instructions. Dive into its taxonomy of 35 edit operations, multi-turn edit sequences, and a research-only CC BY-NC-ND license that keeps vendors honest. Learn how tools like FLUX SRPO I2I slot in, plus what you should be asking your vendors right now. Get a roadmap for future-proofing your stack, from instruction schemas to edge device privacy. Real data, better control, and workflow wins—just don’t melt the hands.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251028042459700+-+pico_banana_dataset.mp3" length="4088880" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761649345848</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251028042459700+-+pico_banana_dataset-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Fast Model with Receipts: Nemotron Nano 2 Goes Open Source</title>
    <description><![CDATA[NVIDIA’s open source Nemotron Nano 2 just dropped and it’s not your average small model. Packed as NIM microservices, it moves fast from “demo” to “daily workflow,” running on everything from vLLM to llama.cpp. Toggle internal reasoning with “thinking traces” for both transparency and speed. Perfect for content creators, agent devs, and ops teams who want fast, reliable, and scalable automation. Explore use cases like editorial planning, ad ops, and pipeline magic. Pro tips on guardrails, governance, and how to keep costs under control while scaling up smart automation. The episode features pricing, integration tips, and how to actually deploy small, open models without the usual headaches.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:18:03 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251029072724178+-+nemotron_nano_2_open.mp3" length="3475344" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1761740283511</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251029072724178+-+nemotron_nano_2_open-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Claude Haiku 4.5: Fast, Cheap, and Uncanny</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude Haiku 4.5 has entered the chat and it’s setting a new speed record for generative AI workflows. With blazing-fast performance, aggressive pricing, and structured outputs, Haiku is positioned as the go-to model for everyday drafting, tagging, and extracting via Anthropic’s API or Google Vertex AI. Learn how creators, marketers, and ops teams can automate titles, summaries, docs, ad copy, and more while keeping control with function calling and predictable schemas. Plus, the real-world trade-offs between closed models like Haiku and open alternatives such as Qwen3 and DeepSeek. Streamline your stack, batch content jobs, and let AI handle the grunt work so your team can focus on what matters.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:22:26 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251031195501069+-+claude_haiku_45_magic.mp3" length="3743736" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762014146553</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251031195501069+-+claude_haiku_45_magic-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Emu3.5: The Model That Paints With Plot Twists</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Explore Emu3.5 from BAAI, the newest open-weight, native multimodal model that generates images and text in a single loop. Dive into how its supercharged DiDA speed claims could unlock true batch production for creators and teams, and why interleaved generation means fewer copy-paste fumbles. Learn where DIY tinkerers win, where production houses get an upgrade, and what pitfalls and possibilities emerge with open access. Break down workflow boosts, new campaign formats, and the future of image-to-anything at human scale. Real advice for anyone experimenting with high-volume creative pipelines or managing huge multimedia libraries.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251101133059395+-+emu3_5_plot_twists.mp3" length="3708456" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762033893735</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251101133059395+-+emu3_5_plot_twists-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Everything’s Bigger in Texas: GPU Gold Rush for AI Creators</title>
    <description><![CDATA[AI compute is having a Texas-sized glow-up as Microsoft secures major GPU capacity with IREN and OpenAI gears up to ride AWS’s freshest accelerators. What does that mean for creators, marketers, and operators? Get ready for faster, smoother video and content workflows, less time in queue purgatory, and more concurrency when campaigns heat up. Dive into how new hardware like NVIDIA’s GB200 and GB300 unlock next-level multimodal rendering, what “agent teamwork” means for your pipeline, and why version pinning and creative metrics are now table stakes. Plus, get the download on recent model launches and learn the new playbook to maximize throughput, maintain creative control, and stay portable across vendors. It’s queue freedom, cowboy style.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:16:02 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251103175241815+-+texas_gpu_goldrush.mp3" length="3554784" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762211762408</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251103175241815+-+texas_gpu_goldrush-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Agents, Edge, and Multimodals: Qwen3-Max, Ming-Flash, Open VL</title>
    <description><![CDATA[AI workflows just leveled up. This episode spotlights Qwen3-Max “Thinking” (closed, API only) as it shifts agentic reasoning from turn-based chat to actual planning and tool use. Hear why small vision-language models like open Qwen3-VL are making privacy, cost, and latency wins possible for image and doc triage. Explore Ming-Flash-Omni-Preview on Hugging Face bringing mixture-of-experts magic to video, text, and audio understanding—even if it’s early days. Rounding it out is MagicPathAI’s prompt-to-prototype UI sneak peek for serious design-to-code speed. Get quick, real-life pilots for marketers, creators, and ops. The hybrid AI stack is here: route, plan, tag, review. Human plus machine always.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 12:31:49 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251104070304500+-+agents_edge_multimodal.mp3" length="3640032" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762259509844</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251104070304500+-+agents_edge_multimodal-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Chutes and Ladders: OpenAI Swaps Go Live</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Chutes is bringing open-source models to OpenAI-compatible endpoints, letting creators and marketers instantly swap in alternatives like DeepSeek‑R1 with just a base URL change. No need to rebuild your stack or decode new APIs—just plug in and roll. Get cost savings and resilience without sacrificing convenience. We break down hands-on automation recipes for content ops, copy, and creative, cover competitive angle vs hosts like Together and Groq, and share workflow tips for minimizing spend. Learn why model-agnostic routing, budget controls, and failovers are becoming standard in modern automation. If your stack already speaks OpenAI, boring just got brilliant.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:10:04 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251105202255621+-+chutes_openai_swap.mp3" length="3093216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762467004903</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251105202255621+-+chutes_openai_swap-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Open Playbook: Kimi K2 &amp; HunyuanWorld-Mirror Deep Dive</title>
    <description><![CDATA[AI workflows leap forward with two major China-born releases. Moonshot’s Kimi K2 Thinking brings “do the thing” automation—plan, fetch, summarize, validate, post—letting creators and marketers run multi-step projects with just enough human gatekeeping. It fits right into tool stacks, from Make to custom scripts, and can be self-hosted for privacy and control. Tencent’s open source HunyuanWorld-Mirror flips videos and photo bursts into ready-to-use 3D scenes. Product teams, AR/VR builders, and ops get fast photogrammetry, Unity and Unreal integration, and all the audit trails. We tackle practical setups, cost compression, and where small-but-smart models and open pipelines are outpacing closed stacks. Plus, cheeky tongue twisters and near-future pilot ideas.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:38:33 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251108085947402+-+kimi_k2_hunyuanworld.mp3" length="3706224" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762612713211</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251108085947402+-+kimi_k2_hunyuanworld-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Bananas for GEMPIX2: Google’s Image Model Rumor Mill</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Google’s internal image model, aka Nano Banana 2 or GEMPIX2, has the AI grapevine buzzing but not spilling the docs. We unpack what matters for creators and marketers: cleaner text-in-image, higher resolutions, and true brand consistency could finally hit the campaign production line. Get the rundown on expected API integrations for Gemini and Vertex, the pragmatic workflow upgrades you can prep for now, and why batch factories and scoring systems will matter more than pretty leaks. Plus a lightning round: recent market pivots, live AI translation shocks, and what it means for cost, control, and human-in-the-loop creativity.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 14:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251109080029511+-+bananas_gempix2_rumor.mp3" length="3052608" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1762696921534</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251109080029511+-+bananas_gempix2_rumor-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>GPT-5.1: Instant Wins or Thinking Things Through?</title>
    <description><![CDATA[OpenAI just dropped GPT-5.1 and creators everywhere are about to move at warp speed. Explore how the new “Instant” and “Thinking” modes in ChatGPT unlock faster first drafts and smarter, deeper workflow upgrades for marketers, content teams, and automators. Learn how to route between them, set up safeguard critics, and avoid surprise costs. Get the playbook for putting model selection, variant caps, and policy-as-code into real ops—plus the state of model competition, from Anthropic’s billion-dollar moves to DeepSeek’s budget shake-up. Find out why the future is about adaptive AI that delivers work you can trust, not just speed and hype.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 02:28:15 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251112202646728+-+gpt51_instant_thinking.mp3" length="3352224" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763000895276</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251112202646728+-+gpt51_instant_thinking-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>ERNIE 5.0: Multimodal Mania and Marketing Magic</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Dive into Baidu’s ERNIE 5.0—a model built to understand text, images, audio, and video as one seamless brain. Explore what “native full-modal” means, the creative perks (cross-format consistency, fewer prompt chains, and tighter factuality), and where to watch for trade-offs like latency and asset costs. We tackle ops moves like routing tasks between models, region rules, rights management, and how marketers can build smarter automation layers on top. Get KPIs for pilots, tips for prompt structure, and real talk on moderation and data residency. Plus, hear about the first AI song to top Billboard and why China’s energy surge could shift global AI economics.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 11:06:20 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251114053843029+-+ernie_5_marketing_magic.mp3" length="3969504" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763118380736</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251114053843029+-+ernie_5_marketing_magic-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Anthropic’s Open Source Vibe Check for AI Neutrality</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Anthropic just dropped an open source framework for auditing political neutrality in language models—and it’s way more than “trust us bro.” This episode breaks down how to stress-test your AI’s even-handedness using paired prompts and structured scoring, why it matters for marketers and creators running automated content at scale, and how to bake neutrality ops into your workflows. From scoring thresholds to clever vendor games, setting up guardrails, internationalizing your prompt packs, and even A/B switching fallback models, get the playbook for scaling transparent, audit-ready content pipelines. Includes quick tips for lean teams, tips for catching failure modes like sarcasm or hidden leans in microcopy, and why transparent audit trails will soon be table stakes.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 19:38:55 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251115061700566+-+anthropic_vibe_check.mp3" length="3500592" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763321935406</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251115061700566+-+anthropic_vibe_check-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Qwen, Grok, and GPT-5.1: Who&apos;s Next to Run Your Workflow?</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Alibaba’s Qwen app is opening doors for marketers in China with deep integrations and real workflow hooks, but when should global teams jump in? Grok goes free and sparks talk about the fastest ways to build real-world AI automations using tools like n8n, Make.com, and Langfuse. GPT-5.1 lands with smart heuristics for balancing speed and judgment. Hear practical KPIs for workflow automation, vendor lock-in risks, the rise of assistants as control planes, and why Google and photonic computing could quietly change your productivity stack. Stay one step ahead on localization, compliance, and the connector game.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 04:26:19 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251117222437982+-+qwen_grok_gpt_workflow.mp3" length="3946656" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763439979851</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251117222437982+-+qwen_grok_gpt_workflow-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Pushing Buttons: Gemini 3, Veo 3 Fast, and Antigravity for Workflows</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Dive into real-world automation with Gemini 3, Veo 3 Fast, and Google’s Antigravity IDE for creators and marketers. This episode breaks down what’s mature now for AI agents and where humans still need guardrails. Get clear strategies for evaluating agent safety, integration, and brand controls at scale. Hear the latest on cost control, vendor lock-in risks, governing AI outputs, and how to wrap workflows with API accountability, not demo UIs. Plus, get a pulse on the multi-billion dollar moves shaping the generative AI ecosystem. If you want to scale creative output while avoiding the newest AI chaos, this is your action plan.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251118161948426+-+pushing_buttons_gemini3.mp3" length="3490632" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763503443067</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251118161948426+-+pushing_buttons_gemini3-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Plug Into Gemini 3, SAM 3, and CORE-1 Workflows</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Google’s Gemini 3, Meta’s SAM 3, and Octane AI’s CORE-1 are shaking up creator and marketer workflows. Dive deep on when to escalate to Gemini 3’s Deep Think mode for campaign planning, why SAM 3’s video segmentation is a game-changer but needs smart caching, and how CORE-1’s agentic commerce rewires ecom experiences with real guardrails. Cuts through the hype about open vs closed models, API orchestration, ROI tracking, and compliance signals. Human-in-the-loop tricks included. Actionable advice for plugging AI into your media, marketing, and ecommerce stack—without burning your ad budget on unnecessary compute.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:28:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251119175420100+-+gemini_sam_core_workflow.mp3" length="3921888" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763594925326</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251119175420100+-+gemini_sam_core_workflow-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Nano Banana Pro vs Gemini 3 Image Smackdown</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Nano Banana Pro just dropped into the Google image stack, and it is officially the mid tier workhorse between Gemini 2.5 Flash Image and Gemini 3 Pro Image. This episode digs into how to pick the right model for campaigns, how to structure prompts with schema patterns, and how to route images through critics, batching, and upscaling to cut costs. Hear real world tactics for AI FinOps, transparency and alpha workflows, brand safe guardrails, and contract language that protects your assets. Plus a fast look at Nvidia earnings, Musk and Nvidia’s Saudi supercomputer project, and the Trump administration push to centralize AI regulation.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:24:05 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251120131543555+-+nano_banana_pro_ep.mp3" length="6175320" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763670245258</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251120131543555+-+nano_banana_pro_ep-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Grok, Guardrails, and Fibonacci Fails</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Grok’s Holocaust denial fallout puts AI safety in the spotlight. This episode breaks down what builders, marketers, and media operators should actually do when a model crosses the line. Learn how to design real guardrails, write honest system cards, and run multilingual red‑team testing. Get practical checklists for product, safety, marketing, and engineering teams, from kill switches and brand‑safe tiers to refusal analytics and crisis comms. Plus a quick news sweep on GPT‑5.1, Gemini 3, SAM 3, Anthropic’s audits, and why model routers, shadow mode, and AI FinOps are now table stakes for any serious automation workflow.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 13:16:37 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251123074021093+-+grok_guardrails_fibo.mp3" length="3748680" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1763903797528</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251123074021093+-+grok_guardrails_fibo-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Gemini 3 vs The Hype: Model Wars for Real Workflows</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Google Gemini 3 is getting “I’m not going back” hype from Marc Benioff, but should teams actually switch from ChatGPT yet. This episode breaks down how to evaluate Gemini 3 and other frontier models against real workflows for creators and marketers. Learn how to design a model agnostic stack with API shims, routers, and strict schemas, what to put in a Model Rider for your contracts, and how to run practical benchmarks. Plus quick hits on Claude Opus 4.5, the Genesis Mission executive order, and Amazon’s massive AI infra bet.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 13:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251125074000455+-+gemini_3_model_wars.mp3" length="3462072" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1764075918611</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251125074000455+-+gemini_3_model_wars-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>FLUX.2, Cake Day, and Killing Boring Creative Ops</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Deep dive into FLUX.2 for creators and marketers who care about automation, compliance, and shipping faster. Covers what “open weight” really means, how to treat FLUX.2 dev as an R and D sandbox, and when to upgrade to commercial endpoints like pro. Breaks down production readiness signals, multi reference use cases, typography tests, and local versus hosted trade offs. Walks through policy as code, consent, brand safety critics, and the KPIs that prove structured generation beats vibes. Ends with a tactical checklist to pilot FLUX.2 without nuking your budget or your legal team’s weekend.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251126140936355+-+flux2_cake_day_ops.mp3" length="4032696" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1764185460209</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251126140936355+-+flux2_cake_day_ops-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Z-Image vs Midjourney vs SD3: Who Runs Your Studio</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Alibaba’s open Z-Image model is gunning for Midjourney and Stable Diffusion Three on photoreal image generation. This episode breaks down what actually matters for teams shipping assets at scale: quality, speed, GPU requirements, and total cost per image. Learn where Z-Image shines on local workstations, how to wire it into automated thumbnail and product shot pipelines, and why prompt understanding, controllability, and text rendering still need guardrails. We also cover evaluation tactics, multi-agent critic workflows inspired by OpenGradient Council Mode, creative “vibe coder” roles, and practical governance around IP, deepfakes, and C2PA. Plus, a quick look at HAiO and 0G’s iProducer iNFTs for automated music and cover art workflows.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 20:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251129120502069+-+z_image_image_stack.mp3" length="3507984" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1764449672450</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251129120502069+-+z_image_image_stack-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Runway Gen-4.5 vs The Rest of the Reel World</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Runway Gen 4.5 just dropped and the benchmark charts are loud, but what actually matters for creators is workflow. This episode breaks down how Gen 4.5 stacks up against Sora 2, Veo 3, Pika, and Luma for real marketing pipelines. Learn when to use image to video, video to video, and text to video for brand safe ads, b roll, and social refreshes. Get practical governance tactics for deepfake risk, uncanny humans, and legal review. Hear how teams are structuring roles like prompt director and AI compositor, why cost per approved asset beats cost per render, and when open source video models like Open Sora and HunyuanVideo make sense in house.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:56:38 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251201213118718+-+runway_gen_4_5_workflow.mp3" length="3369624" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1764644198916</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251201213118718+-+runway_gen_4_5_workflow-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Pick Your AI Fighter: GPT 5.2 vs Gemini vs DeepSeek</title>
    <description><![CDATA[GPT 5.2, Gemini, DeepSeek, routers, and agents all walked into the same week. This episode breaks down when to use GPT 5.2 Instant, Thinking, or Pro for marketing ops, analytics, and high stakes reporting. It compares DeepSeek V3.2 and Speciale against GPT and Gemini for reasoning heavy tasks and open weight deployment. It covers Gemini Deep Research, the Interactions API, and practical patterns to reduce hallucinations with retrieval and verification. It also hits vendor lock in strategies, agent frameworks like LangGraph and CrewAI, Google’s emotion aware TTS for localization, and the real operational and regulatory costs behind “free” models.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 01:32:02 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251212202945319+-+pick_your_ai_fighter.mp3" length="4351512" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1765589522191</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251212202945319+-+pick_your_ai_fighter-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Agents.md, Ad Overviews, and Cocoa Chaos</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Agent standards are heating up and the martech stack is feeling it. This episode breaks down the Linux Foundation Agentic AI Foundation, OpenAI’s agents.md style spec, and why “standards” might either unlock interoperability or just tighten vendor lock in. The conversation connects agent governance to real workflows like lifecycle marketing, customer support, and CRM write access. It also covers CleverTap’s Agentic AI pitch, the risks of autonomous campaign optimization, and how ads are shifting into AI search and chat experiences. Expect practical guardrail advice for permissions, kill switches, read only first setups, and why clean product data and answer ready messaging decide whether assistants actually recommend you.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 13:42:54 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251213074858005+-+agents_md_cocoa_chaos.mp3" length="3750744" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1765633374348</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251213074858005+-+agents_md_cocoa_chaos-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>AI Ads Win, Honesty Hurts</title>
    <description><![CDATA[AI generated beauty ads are now outperforming human creative on click through rate, until people find out they are AI made. This episode breaks down why fully AI generated ads beat human and hybrid workflows, what the “disclosure penalty” means for marketers, and how to frame AI use without tanking performance. It also digs into Salesforce Agentforce 360 observability for marketing agents, and what real auditability should track. Finally, it covers the latest OpenAI vendor data breach and a practical playbook for keeping customer data out of every shiny AI tool while still automating workflows.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:25:18 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251214104237733+-+ai_ads_disclosure.mp3" length="3698448" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1765729518708</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251214104237733+-+ai_ads_disclosure-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Disney Sora Deals and AI Ads With Leash On</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Disney is licensing hundreds of Disney Marvel Star Wars and Pixar characters into OpenAI Sora which unlocks brand safe generative video while tightening control over how IP gets used. The conversation digs into what this means for creators who want licensed chaos versus open source freedom and how pipelines will change. It also covers Google Ads new AI Advisors how to safely offload PPC grunt work without burning budgets and why marketers are becoming system supervisors. Finally it breaks down ads inside AI search and chat why clicks matter less how to win citations inside answers and why structured content and clean data now drive distribution.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:46:43 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251215130023144+-+disney_sora_ai_ads.mp3" length="3746160" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1765824403788</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251215130023144+-+disney_sora_ai_ads-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>GPT 5.2, Nemotron 3, Raven 3 and Chocolate Workflows</title>
    <description><![CDATA[GPT 5.2, NVIDIA Nemotron 3 open weights, and PolyAI Raven 3 are reshaping how creators and marketers automate work. This episode breaks down what GPT 5.2’s Instant, Thinking, and Pro modes actually mean for content and campaign workflows, and how to validate “reasoning” with artifacts, structure, and second pass checks. Learn where Nemotron 3 fits in open agent stacks, why orchestration and shared schemas matter, and how to avoid vendor lock in. Then dive into Raven 3 for voice automation, escalation pitfalls, and hybrid handoff patterns that keep humans in the loop while AI handles repetitive calls.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:07:18 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251216130012394+-+gpt_nemotron_raven.mp3" length="3251448" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1765919238993</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251216130012394+-+gpt_nemotron_raven-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Google AI Overviews Now With Microtransactions</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Google is testing ads directly inside AI Overviews and AI Mode, turning the answer box into prime ad real estate. Hunter and Riley break down what happens when one synthesized AI verdict also carries sponsored picks, and how that impacts trust across search. They dig into Performance Max workflows, brand safety, and why structured, proof-backed content becomes survival gear. The conversation zooms out to Gemini 3 Flash as the default AI Mode engine, NVIDIA Nemotron 3 as a rising open source option, hybrid model stacks, and why creators need systems that protect truth, not just tools that generate content.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:28:12 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251217130044141+-+google_ai_overviews.mp3" length="3562488" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1765996092872</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251217130044141+-+google_ai_overviews-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>AI Answers, Sponsored: Agents, Advisors, and Lock In</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Microsoft pulls Azure AI Foundry into VS Code so teams can build, evaluate, and ship AI assistants without living in twelve dashboards. Google launches Ads Advisor and Analytics Advisor while quietly testing sponsored placements inside AI Mode, blending ads directly into AI answers. PubMatic and Butler Till push agentic AI for connected TV, raising big questions about guardrails, brand safety, and kill switches. The conversation digs into real agent behavior versus rebranded automation, how to use advisor tools like a junior analyst, what AI native SEO and measurement look like, and which marketing jobs get upgraded as agents start handling the grunt work.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20251218130010356+-+sponsored_ai_answers.mp3" length="4548120" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1766088639317</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20251218130010356+-+sponsored_ai_answers-studio-crop.jpg"/>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
