<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <channel>
    <title>COEY Cast</title>
    <link>https://coey.com/resources/podcast</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 COEY</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:04:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <itunes:category text="Business">
      <itunes:category text="Entrepreneurship"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Technology">
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>

    <generator>RSS Builder</generator>

    <!-- Show description -->
    <description>
      COEY Cast is your daily download on AI and automation. We break down the latest in generative models, intelligent workflows, and emerging tools—giving marketers, operators, and business leaders the insights they need to move faster and scale smarter. From AI video and audio to end-to-end automation pipelines, each episode turns complex breakthroughs into clear, actionable takeaways you can actually use.
    </description>

    <!-- iTunes / Apple Podcasts tags -->
    <itunes:author>COEY</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
      COEY Cast is your daily download on AI and automation. We break down the latest in generative models, intelligent workflows, and emerging tools—giving marketers, operators, and business leaders the insights they need to move faster and scale smarter. From AI video and audio to end-to-end automation pipelines, each episode turns complex breakthroughs into clear, actionable takeaways you can actually use.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/brand-assets/coey-cast-logo.jpg"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>COEY</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>ted@coey.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

    <!-- Atom self-link -->
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ted-coey/coey-cast/main/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <!-- Episodes will be inserted here as <item> blocks -->

  <item>
    <title>Qwen3-Max-Preview: Scaling to a Trillion &amp; Beyond</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This week, we put Alibaba’s Qwen3-Max-Preview to the test—a trillion-parameter upgrade promising smoother instruction following, longer conversational threads, and genuine tool-calling power for creators and teams. We discuss what “scaling works” actually means for daily workflows: less prompt wrangling, better agents for chaining tasks, and practical examples like video content pipelines and brand campaigns. We break down the differences from previous Qwen3 models, compare real-world pros and cons, and share best practices for validation, safety, and using multi-step automations. By the end, you’ll know how Qwen3-Max-Preview can streamline content ops and whether it’s worth plugging into your stack, solo or at scale.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 22:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250906175146600+-+qwen3_max_scaling_vibes.mp3" length="4197360" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757196141766</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250906175146600+-+qwen3_max_scaling_vibes.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Seven Ways to Keep Your AI Video in Line: Vidu Q1 Update</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This episode dives into the massive Reference-to-Video update for ShengShu Technology’s Vidu Q1 model, which now lets users upload up to seven reference images per sequence. Hunter and Riley unpack what this means for creators, brands, and indie studios striving for true shot-to-shot consistency in AI-generated video. They explore how multiple references help lock character identity, props, wardrobe, and backgrounds, reducing the notorious continuity drift. Expect a breakdown of workflow tips, common pitfalls, competitive comparisons with Runway and Luma, use cases from social content to ad pipelines, and where this tech sits in the growing stack for marketers and content teams. Don’t miss practical advice on setting up your own "reference kit".]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:17:54 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250908170128634+-+vidu_q1_seven_refs.mp3" length="4689288" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757366274333</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250908170128634+-+vidu_q1_seven_refs.jpg"/>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Firefly Boards &amp; Model 4: Idea to Approval Fast-Tracked</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Today, we battle test Microsoft VibeVoice 7B and dive deep into Adobe’s Firefly Image Model 4 and Firefly Boards. Discover what makes Model 4 a leap ahead for creatives. Hands and eyes look human, image quality is up, and styles stay consistent across channels and platforms. Firefly Boards lets you co-create, share, get feedback, and iterate— all right inside Creative Cloud, without back-and-forth emails. Automation tips abound: learn to trigger batch image and video generation from intake forms, streamline approvals, and nail brand consistency. Pros, cons, and practical workflow hacks for solo creators, marketers, and global teams are covered. Plus, the automation blueprint to get your campaigns from prompt to publish with less busywork.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/20250909185413964+-+firefly_boards_model4.mp3" length="3478248" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757459079525</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Image+20250909185413964+-+firefly_boards_model4.jpg"/>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
