<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <channel>
    <title>COEY Cast</title>
    <link>https://coey.com/podcast</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 COEY</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:41:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
     <itunes:category text="Business">
       <itunes:category text="Entrepreneurship"/>
     </itunes:category>
     <itunes:category text="Technology">
       <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
     </itunes:category>
    <generator>RSS Builder</generator>
    <description>
      Blue Lightning AI Daily is your go-to AI podcast for creators, delivering fast, focused updates on the world of generative AI. We cover the latest breakthroughs in large language models (LLMs), AI video editing, AI photography, AI audio tools, and creative automation. Each episode gives digital creators, content marketers, and creative professionals clear insights into how AI is transforming storytelling, production, and the creator economy. Stay informed, stay creative, and stay ahead with daily AI news made simple.
    </description>

    <!-- iTunes / Apple Podcasts tags -->
    <itunes:author>Blue Lightning</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
      Blue Lightning AI Daily is your go-to AI podcast for creators, delivering fast, focused updates on the world of generative AI. 
      We cover the latest breakthroughs in LLMs, AI video, AI audio, and creative tools.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://blue-lighting-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/blue-lighting-cover.jpg"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Blue Lightning</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>ted@coey.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

    <!-- Atom self-link (recommended for apps like Apple Podcasts / Overcast) -->
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ted-coey/bluelightingpodcast/main/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <!-- Episodes will be inserted here as <item> blocks -->


  <item>
    <title>Databricks Assistant Grows Up: Workflows, Hacks, and Recipies</title>
    <description><![CDATA[We break down the Agentic glow-up of Databricks Assistant—now a real workflow operator for marketers, creators, and data nerds alike! Learn fresh automation hacks, API workarounds, and three creator playbooks to ditch dashboard drudgery and boost creative output. Plus, COEY Cast’s spiciest takes on Agent Bricks, data security, and seamless AI-human teamwork. Made with Microsoft VibeVoice 7b!]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:41:52 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/databricks_assistant_glowup.mp3" length="4816896" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1757112112370</guid>
    <itunes:image href="https://coey-podcast.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Podcast+Image+-+databricks_assistant_glowup.jpg"/>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
